(Sheldon:)Hello?
(Raj:)Stupid Aquaman.
(Leonard:)If it makes you
feel any better,
(Leonard:)when I was dating Penny,
(Leonard:)she used to flip out
on me all the time.
(Zack:)Whoa. You dated Penny?
(Leonard:)She didn't tell you?
(Zack:)She told me she dated
a guy named Leonard.
(Zack:)Who would have
thought it was you?
(Leonard:)Who else would it be?
(Zack:)I don't know. Somebody
bigger and...
(Zack:)Yeah, sure.
Why not you?
(Sheldon:)I may have failed.
(Howard:)Okay, I guess we just go
without a Wonder Woman.
(Zack:)I don't want to go
without Penny.
(Raj:)Oh, great. No Superman,
no Wonder Woman?
(Raj:)All we've got is a skinny Flash,
(Raj:)an Indian Aquaman,
(Raj:)a nearsighted
Green Lantern,